Guide to the The Nick Zedd Papers, 1963 - 2016 MSS.311
Fales Library and Special Collections
- Series II: Projects
  - Subseries C: Interviews
    - "Nick Zedd Interview" by Neil for Dirt Number 4 [Zine], Fall 1992 (Box 7, Folder 62)
    - "Nick Zedd Interview" by Nick Walker [Incomplete], December 17, 2000 (Box 7, Folder 63)
    - "Nick Zedd Interview" for Pussy! Number 12 [Zine], c2003 (Box 7, Folder 64)
    - "Nick Zedd Interview" for Rage [Magazine, Norway], c1994 (Box 7, Folder 65)
    - "Nick Zedd Interview" by Sic Mic and Barb Morrison for Lowlife: Rock Magazine Number 10 [Zine], 1986 (Box 7, Folder 66)
    - "Nick Zedd the Interview: You Talkin' to Me?" by Jay Bliznick for The 1996 Chicago Underground Film Festival [Program Magazine] (Box 7, Folder 67)
    - "Nick Zedd: Master of Transgression" by Dirk de Bruyn, c1989 (Box 8, Folder 1)
    - "Nick Zedd: What He Said" by T.R. Loviscek for Graffiti Volume 4, Number 7, c1987 (Box 8, Folder 2)
    - "Nick Zedd's Not Dead" for Lollygag Number 3 [Zine], 2009 (Box 8, Folder 3)
    - "Night of the Living Zedd: Underground Filmmaker Confuses Whitmyre" by William Lindsey, February 27, 2006 (Box 8, Folder 4)
    - "Number One With a Bolex: Beyond the Myth of Nick Zedd" by Gene Suicide for Sex & Guts Issue 2 [Manuscript with Zine], 1997 - 1998 (Box 8, Folder 5)
    - "The Only Interview with Nick Zedd That Doesn't Mention Lydia Lunch" by Zietgiest for Kinder & Gentler, c1990 (Box 8, Folder 6)
    - "Prattfolio Alumni Newsmakers: Nick Zedd" [Magazine], Fall 1999 (Box 8, Folder 7)
    - "The Problem with Nick" by Billski for Snack [Zine], March 30, 1986 (Box 8, Folder 8)
    - "Raising the Zedd: An Interview with Nick Zedd" by David E. Williams, undated (Box 8, Folder 9)
    - "Rattling Around Inside Zedd's Head" by Carmen Vendelin for Blimp Number 35, c1995 (Box 8, Folder 10)
    - "Return of the Living Zedd" by Jenny Gonzalez and Lisa Darrow-Badavi for Brutarian Number 35, 2000 (Box 8, Folder 11)
    - "Richard Kern and Nick Zedd Are Two Sick Fuckers" by Barry Sublapse for Unsound [Manuscript], c1986 (Box 8, Folder 12)
    - "The Sprinkle Salon: Nick Zedd - Filmmaker, Lovemaker, Soultaker" by Annie Sprinkle for Adam Volume 34, Number 1 [Magazine], January 1990 (Box 8, Folder 13)
    - "Today's Pornography is Tomorrow's Art: An Interview with Nick Zedd" by Bob Moricz for NY Waste, November 2000 (Box 8, Folder 14)
    - "Transgressing Cinema: Going to Hell with Nick Zedd" by Carmen Vendelin, April 1996 (Box 8, Folder 15)
    - "Underground Filmmaker Nick Zedd" by Jeri Rossi for Recreational Vehicle: Ego Issue, Spring 1989 (Box 8, Folder 16)
    - "Underground Hedonist: Nick Zedd" by Annie Sprinkle for All Men [Magazine], May 1991 (Box 8, Folder 17)
    - [Untitled Interview Transcript], c1999 (Box 8, Folder 18)
    - "Who Started the Rumors of Your Death and Why?" [Interview Transcript], c1992 (Box 8, Folder 19)
    - "You Killed Me First: The Cinema of Transgression" -- Various Interviews, February 2012 (Box 35, Folder 11)
    - "Yours Cruelly, Nick Zedd" in Dead Meat Issue 1 [Zine], 1987 (Box 8, Folder 20)
    - "A Zedd and Two Naughts: Canada Does It to Nick Zedd" by Kieran Mahon for Cannibal Culture Issue 3 [Zine], Fall 1998 (Box 8, Folder 21)
    - "Zedd is Not Dead" by Hugh Gallagher for Draculina Number 12 [Zine], 1991 (Box 8, Folder 22)
    - "Zedd is Not Dead: The Whys and Wares of Nick Zedd" by Jay Sosnicki for Nuthing Sacred Number 5 [Manuscript and Zine], September 1992 (Box 8, Folder 23)
  - Subseries D: Ads, Reviews and Literature
    - "The Adventures of Electra Elf" [Press], 2003 - 2006 (Box 8, Folder 24)
    - Bleed [Press], 1992 - 1993 (Box 8, Folder 25)
    - "The Cinema of Transgression" by Ernie Birk for ZAT: 1st Anniversary Issue Number 5 [Manuscript and Magazine], 1985 (Box 8, Folder 26)
    - "Cinema of Transgression Parts 1 and 2" by Cricket Delembard for Draculina Numbers 13 -14 [Zines], 1992 (Box 8, Folder 27)
    - [Cinema of Transgression Press], various (Box 8, Folder 28)
    - [Cinema of Transgression - International Press], various (Box 8, Folder 29)
    - "Cinema of Transgression" for Offrande Number 6 [Magazine, France], October - November 1994 (Box 8, Folder 30)
    - "Cinema of Transgression" for Rage [Magazine, Norway], c1992 (Box 8, Folder 31)
    - "Cinema Underground USA" for Decoder Number 3 [Magazine, Italy], c1987 (Box 8, Folder 32)
    - "Geek Maggot Bingo" [Press], c1983 (Box 8, Folder 33)
    - Goteborg Poetry Art Festival [Press, Sweden], 1988 (Box 8, Folder 34)
    - "Lord of the Cockrings" [Press], 2002 (Box 8, Folder 35)
    - "Nick Zedd Eulogy" for Ben is Dead: Black Issue Number 24, Summer 1994 (Box 8, Folder 36)
    - [Nick Zedd International Press Pack], 1990 (Box 8, Folder 37)
    - "No Such Thing as Gravity" by Alyce Wittenstein [Press], c1990 (Box 8, Folder 38)
    - "Notes on the Work of Nick Zedd" by Jonas Mekas [Manuscript], undated (Box 8, Folder 39)
    - "Police State" [Press], c1991 (Box 8, Folder 40)
    - "Screen Tests" [Press], 1998 (Box 8, Folder 41)
    - "Shadows in the City" by Ari Roussimoff [Press], c1991 (Box 8, Folder 42)
    - "Thrust in Me" [Press], 1984 - 1986 (Box 8, Folder 43)
    - "Thus Spake Zarathustra" [Press], 2001 (Box 8, Folder 44)
    - "Sex 'n Violence and Music: NY Underground Film" for Journal Film Number 17 [Magazine, Germany], August - September 1988 (Box 8, Folder 45)
    - "They Eat Scum" [Press], various (Box 8, Folder 46)
    - Totem of the Depraved [Press], c1991 (Box 8, Folder 47)
    - Underground Film Bulletin [Press], various (Box 8, Folder 48)
    - "Underground Film Made in U.S.A." for Filmfaust [Magazine, Germany], October - November 1988 (Box 8, Folder 49)
    - "War is Menstrual Envy" [Press], various (Box 8, Folder 50)
    - "Whoregasm" [Press], various (Box 8, Folder 51)
    - "You Killed Me First: The Cinema of Transgression" [Reviews and Ads], February 2012 (Box 35, Folder 12)
    - [Zedd Ads], various (Box 8, Folder 52)
    - [Book Excerpts Featuring Zedd], various (Box 8, Folder 53)
    - If We Die Without Jesus We Shall Go to Hell [Zine], c1993 (Box 8, Folder 54)
    - Subversion: The Definitive History of Underground Cinema by Duncan Reekie [Manuscript], 2007 (Box 8, Folder 55)
  - Subseries E: Other Artists and Events
    - The Armory Show, New York Pier 92, 2010 (Box 8, Folder 56)
    - Artists Space: Remapping Boundaries, March 14 - May 4, 1991 (Box 8, Folder 57)
    - 12th Asian American International Film Festival [French Institute, NY], 1989 (Box 8, Folder 58)
    - "Betaville" by Alyce Wittenstein [Pocket Press Kit], 1988 (Box 8, Folder 59)
    - "Blonde Death" [Press Materials], 1983 (Box 8, Folder 60)
    - Brooklyn Arts and Culture Association, Inc. [Newsletters 8 - 9], 1984 - 1985 (Box 8, Folder 61)
    - "Buffalo '66" by Vincent Gallo [Press Pack], 1998 (Box 8, Folder 62)
    - "Cecil B. Demented" by John Waters [Screening Program], 2000 (Box 8, Folder 63)
    - 6th Annual Chicago Underground Film Festival [Program], 1999 (Box 8, Folder 64)
    - Chicago Underground Film Fest [Program], undated (Box 8, Folder 65)
    - "Every Minute as We Are Talking Films Are Falling to Dust" [Anthology Films Archives Program], c1992 (Box 8, Folder 66)
    - Exposure Future of Film Fest [New York Program], August 4 - 5, 2000 (Box 8, Folder 67)
    - [Flyers], various (Box 8, Folder 68)
    - "Highway of Heartache" by Gregory Wild [Press Pack], 1994 (Box 8, Folder 69)
    - "Kenneth Anger's Icons" [Courthouse Gallery, Anthology Film Archives Program], January 30 - March 2, 1996 (Box 8, Folder 70)
    - "Kinetica 2: Centennial Tribute to Oskar Fischinger" [Program], 2000 (Box 8, Folder 71)
    - 1st Los Angeles International Film Exposition [Programs], November 4 - 14, 1971 (Box 8, Folder 72)
    - "Marcel Marceau with Pierre Verry" [Academy of Music Philadelphia Program], March 28 - 29, 1976 (Box 8, Folder 73)
    - Metro Con [University of Maryland, Program], November 23 - 24, 1973 (Box 8, Folder 74)
    - Millennium Film Workshop Spring Series [Program], 1995 (Box 8, Folder 75)
    - "Multiple Futures and Other Paranoid Fantasies" by Alyce Wittenstein [Press Pack], 1995 (Box 8, Folder 76)
    - Museum of African American History and Arts: Black Film Festival [Program], June 1991 (Box 9, Folder 1)
    - One Arm Red [Brooklyn, NY Calendar], Spring / Summer 2004 (Box 9, Folder 2)
    - Preview: Program Guide to AFI Theater and Member Events, August 1991 (Box 9, Folder 3)
    - "Super 8 Motel" [Lydia Lunch, Richard Kern Program], c1985 (Box 9, Folder 4)
    - "Superstar: The Karen Carpenter Story" by Todd Haynes [Screening Program], 1987 (Box 9, Folder 5)
    - Swedish Avant Garde Film, 1924 - 1990 [Program] (Box 9, Folder 6)
    - "Warp One: My Battlefield, My Body" [Ambassador Theatre Playbill Magazine], February 1973 (Box 9, Folder 7)
    - "Warp: The World's First Science Fiction Epic Adventure Play in Serial Form" [Trinity Theatre, Washington DC Program], undated (Box 9, Folder 8)
- Series III: Correspondence
  Series III: Correspondence preserves communication not directly related to any single production, and is organized alphabetically by individual or company in contact, then chronologically.
  Subseries A: Professional
  Subseries B: Personal
  - Subseries A: Professional
    - [Allin, GG], c1988 (Box 9, Folder 9)
    - [Biafra, Jello], undated (Box 9, Folder 10)
    - [British Film Institute], 1997 - 2003 (Box 9, Folder 11)
    - [Professional Film Distribution], 1982 - 2010 (Box 9, Folder 12)
    - [Death, Donna], circa 1978 (Box 35, Folder 13)
    - [Film Threat], 1986, 1992 - 1996 (Box 9, Folder 13)
    - [Freeland - Hughes, Tessa], 1986 (Box 9, Folder 14)
    - [Genocide, Gia], 1983 - 1985 (Box 9, Folder 15)
    - [Jacobson and Colfin, P.C.], 1995, 2005 (Box 9, Folder 16)
    - [Kern, Richard], 1988 (Box 9, Folder 17)
    - [Lunch, Lydia], 1983 - 1987 (Box 9, Folder 18)
    - [Museum of Modern Art], 1988 - 1989, 1996 - 2001 (Box 9, Folder 19)
    - [Nick Zedd Fan Club Mailing List], undated (Box 9, Folder 20)
    - [Pekar, Harvey], 1985 (Box 9, Folder 21)
    - [Penetration Films], various (Box 9, Folder 22)
    - [Pfahler, Kembra], 1989, 1991 (Box 9, Folder 23)
    - [Press Correspondence], various (Box 9, Folder 24)
    - [Professional Writing Correspondence], 1989 - 2000 (Box 9, Folder 25)
    - [Saint Reverend Jen / Electra Elf], 2002 - 2005 (Box 9, Folder 26)
    - [Underground Film Bulletin], various (Box 9, Folder 27)
    - [Video.com], 1996 - 1997 (Box 9, Folder 28)
    - [Whitney Museum of Art], 1996, 1998 (Box 9, Folder 29)
    - [Waters, John], various (Box 9, Folder 30)
  - Subseries B: Personal
    - [1970s Personal Correspondence], 1972, 1977 (Box 9, Folder 31)
    - [1980s Personal Correspondence], 1980 - 1989 (Box 9, Folder 32)
    - [1990s Personal Correspondence, 1 of 2], 1990 - 1999 (Box 9, Folder 33)
    - [1990s Personal Correspondence, 2 of 2], 1990 - 1999 (Box 9, Folder 34)
    - [2000s Personal Correspondence], 2000 - 2010 (Box 9, Folder 35)
    - [Undated Personal Correspondence] (Box 9, Folder 36)
- Series IV: Dad's Pornography Collection
  Series IV: Dad's Pornography Collection preserves Zedd's father's work as a United States Postal Service censorship researcher. This series is arranged alphabetically by subject and document type.
  - "Censorship - Propaganda - Post Office Dept.", 1959 - 1963 (Box 9, Folder 37)
  - "Contemporary Community Standards" [Assorted Clippings], 1960 - 1964 (Box 9, Folder 38)
  - "Esquire Style Drawings: The Betty Girl Revue", 1937 - 1938 (Box 9, Folder 39)
  - [Lady Chatterly Articles], c1962 (Box 9, Folder 40)
  - [Mail Order Pornography], 1959 - 1961 (Box 9, Folder 41)
  - "Obscenity: Articles and Background Material for Speaking, Research, Etc.", 1969 - 1970 (Box 10, Folder 1)
  - [Pamphlets], 1955 - 1966 (Box 10, Folder 2)
  - [Pornographic Photographs], undated (Box 10, Folder 3)
- Series V: Photography
  Series V: Photography contains photographs, contact sheets, negatives, and slides pertaining to Zedd's productions and personal collection.
  - Subseries A: Professional
    - "The Giant Fly Invincible" by Nick Zedd [film strip], 1969 (Box Binder 1)
    - "Nomad" by Nick Zedd, 1978 (Box Binder 1)
    - "They Eat Scum" by Nick Zedd [Includes other work with Donna Death], 1979 (Box Binder 1)
    - "They Eat Scum" by Nick Zedd [Includes other work with Donna Death], 1979 (Box Binder 2)
    - "The Bogus Man" by Nick Zedd, 1980 (Box Binder 2)
    - "Geet Maggot Bingo" by Nick Zedd, 1983 (Box Binder 2)
    - "The Wild World of Lydia Lunch" by Nick Zedd, 1983 (Box Binder 2)
    - "Kiss Me Goodbye" by Nick Zedd, 1985 (Box Binder 2)
    - "Johnny Satan" by Nick Zedd, c1986 (Box Binder 2)
    - "King of Sex" by Richard Kern, 1986 (Box Binder 3)
    - "King of Sex" by Richard Kern [Mounted Still], 1986 (Box 10, Folder 4)
    - "Police State" by Nick Zedd, 1987 (Box Binder 3)
    - "Whoregasm" by Nick Zedd [Includes other work with Susan Manson], c1988 (Box Binder 3)
    - "Nick Zedd" by Annie Sprinkle, January 1990 (Box 10, Folder 5)
    - "War is Menstrual Envy" by Nick Zedd, 1992 (Box Binder 3)
    - "Trilogy of Teri" by Kembra Pfahler, c1990 (Box Binder 4)
    - "Shadows in the City" by Ari Roussimoff, 1990 (Box Binder 4)
    - "Screen Tests / Why Do You Exist" by Nick Zedd, 1998 (Box Binder 4)
    - "Screen Tests / Why Do You Exist" [Stills], 1998 (Box 10, Folder 6)
    - "Ecstasy in Entropy" by Nick Zedd, 1999 (Box Binder 4)
    - "Ecstasy in Entropy" by Nick Zedd, 1999 (Box 10, Folder 7)
    - "Tom Thumb in the Land of Giants" by Nick Zedd, 1999 (Box Binder 4)
    - "Thus Spake Zarathustra" by Nick Zedd, 2001 (Box Binder 4)
    - "The Adventures of Electra Elf" by Saint Reverend Jen and Nick Zedd, 2002 - 2008 (Box Binder 4)
    - "The Adventures of Electra Elf", 2003 (Box 10, Folder 8)
    - [Miscellaneous Production Images], various (Box Binder 4)
    - [Modeling and Press, 1 of 2], various (Box Binder 4)
    - [Modeling and Press, 2 of 2], various (Box Binder 5)
  - Subseries B: Personal
    - [Miscellaneous Talent and Social Events] (Box Binder 6)
    - [Unidentified Female Nude], undated (Box 10, Folder 9)
- Series VI: Illustrations and Artwork
  Series VI: Illustrations and Artwork includes Zedd's original comic illustrations and paintings.
  - Spring Intramurals Flyer, 1977 (Box 10, Folder 10)
  - [Sketches Removed from "Johnny Satan" Sketchbook], undated (Box 10, Folder 11)
  - [Gia Genocide Illustrations], January 1985 (Box 10, Folder 12)
  - [Illustrations of Richard Hell for Underground Film Bulletin], c1985 (Box 10, Folder 13)
  - "A Collection of Original Collages" by Nick Zedd, 1987 - 1990 (Box 10, Folder 14)
    General
    This collection includes 8 collages by Nick Zedd and a description by John McWhinnie.
  - [Males in Logos], undated (Box 10, Folder 15)
  - [New York Marlon Brando Painting], undated (Box 10, Folder 16)
  - "Aber Otto" by Kurt Kren, 1974 (Box 10, Folder 17)
- Series VII: Objects
  Series VII: Objects contains an assortment of props and production materials, Zedd-Casanova Clothing, and "The Mexican Kit."
  Subseries A: Props
  Subseries B: Zedd - Casanova Clothing includes a variety of tops and pleated skirts featuring prints from Zedd's filmography, and the original screenprint stencils. Designed by Nick Zedd and his wife Monica Casanova.
  Subseries C: The Mexican Kit is an assortment of personal items Zedd collectively titled "The Mexican Kit." This assemblage includes a miniature piñata, ornaments, household adornments, sugar skulls, and figurines.
  - Subseries A: Props
    - [Eye Glasses], undated (Box 11, Object ID: 311.2.0001)
    - [Gory Cut-Off Arm], undated (Box 11, Object ID: 311.2.0002)
    - "Blood Thirst Quencher Gourmet Meat Seed" [Small Duncan Hines Container], undated (Box 11, Object ID: 311.2.0003)
    - "Blood Thirst Quencher Gourmet Meat Seed" [Oversized Plastic Utz Jar], undated (Box 11, Object ID: 311.2.0004)
    - Emile Durkheim's Suicide [used for "Thrust in Me"], 1984 (Box 10, Object ID: 311.2.0005, Folder 18)
    - "The Adventures of Electra Elf" Press Passes, undated (Box 10, Object ID: 311.2.0006, Folder 19)
    - Kodak Brownie Movie Camera [Model 2, Number 76], undated (Box 11, Object ID: 311.2.0007)
    - Hollywood Film Co. Film Reel Metal Container, undated (Box 11, Object ID: 311.2.0008)
    - [Film Production Clapboard], undated (Box 11, Object ID: 311.2.0009)
    - [Small Ceramic Face Sculpture], undated (Box 11, Object ID: 311.2.0010)
    - [Punk Doll], undated (Box 11, Object ID: 311.2.0011)
      This object was originally found with the Zedd - Casanova Clothing Designs.
    - [John Waters Pen], undated (Box 11, Object ID: 311.2.0012)
- Series VIII: Film
  Conditions Governing Access
  Audiovisual materials have not been preserved and may not be available to researchers.
  Series VIII: Film includes original filmic elements by Zedd and is organized chronologically, then alphabetically.
  Subseries A: By Nick Zedd
  Subseries B: Original Containers
  Subseries C: Juvenelia and Family include films Zedd completed as a youth, in addition to a collection of Harding Family movies.
  Subseries D: Miscellaneous includes Lung Leg's "Worm Movie" and a collection of commercial films from Zedd's personal collection.
  Subseries E: Film Documentation includes laboratory forms found with Zedd's original works.
  - Subseries A: By Nick Zedd
    - "Destination X - A Roll", 1976; ID: 311.0003 (Film 311.0003)
      Format: 16mm
      TRT: [unknown]
    - "Nomad", c1978; ID: 311.0004 (Film 311.0004)
    - "They Eat Scum - Spliced Original Reel 1 of 2", 1979; ID: 311.0006 (Film 311.0006)
      Format: Super 8mm
    - "They Eat Scum - Spliced Original Reel 2 of 2", 1979; ID: 311.0007a (Film 311.0007a)
    - "They Eat Scum - Spliced Original Reel 2 of 2", 1979; ID: 311.0007b (Film 311.0007b)
      Format: Super 8
    - "They Eat Scum - Outtakes", 1979; ID: 311.0008 (Film 311.0008)
    - "The Bogus Man", 1980; ID: 311.0002a (Film 311.0002a)
      Originally found with 311.0002b: "Skeleton - Nick Zedd."
    - "Skeleton - Nick Zedd", 1980; ID: 311.0002b (Film 311.0002b)
      Removed from 311.0002a: "The Bogus Man" Print. This was possibly used as leader.
    - "Geek Maggot Bingo - Pix Trk 1 of 4", 1983; ID: 311.0009 (Film 311.0009)
      TRT: unknown
    - "Geek Maggot Bingo - Trk", 1983; ID: 311.0010 (Film 311.0010)
    - [Geek Maggot Bingo - Unlabeled], 1983; ID: 311.0011 (Film 311.0011)
    - "Geek Maggot Bingo - R1 Color Positive", 1983; ID: 311.0012 (Film 311.0012)
    - "Geek Maggot Bingo - R1 Opt. Trk Tail", 1983; ID: 311.0013 (Film 311.0013)
    - "Geek Maggot Bingo - R3 Opt Trk Head", 1983; ID: 311.0014 (Film 311.0014)
    - "Geek Maggot Bingo - R3 Pos Rev Color w/Mag Sound, 'B'-Wind Pix", 1983; ID: 311.0015 (Film 311.0015)
    - "The Wild World of Lydia Lunch - Original", 1984; ID: 311.0016 (Film 311.0016)
    - "Police State - Fill", 1987; ID: 311.0026 (Film 311.0026)
    - "Police State - HHKK", 1987; ID: 311.0028 (Film 311.0028)
    - "Police State - Scene Two Dailies PIX HD", 1987; ID: 311.0032 (Film 311.0032)
    - "Police State - Junk Footage Scene Two", 1987; ID: 311.0033 (Box Binder 3, Media ID: 311.0033)
    - "Police State - Work Pix Dupe", 1987; ID: 311.0034 (Film 311.0034)
    - "Police State - Work Pix HD", 1987; ID: 311.0035 (Film 311.0035)
    - "Police State - Nick's Face", 1987; ID: 311.0036 (Box Binder 3, Media ID: 311.0036)
    - "Police State - Credits", 1987; ID: 311.0037 (Film 311.0037)
    - "Police State - Fill" [Unmarked Reel], 1987; ID: 311.0038 (Film 311.0038)
    - "Police State - Fill" [Blank], 1987; ID: 311.0039 (Film 311.0039)
    - "Police State - Dial A", 1987; ID: 311.0040 (Film 311.0040)
    - "Police State - Dial B", 1987; ID: 311.0041 (Film 311.0041)
    - "Police State - B-Wind Op. Track Head", c1987; ID: 311.0447 (Film 311.0447)
      TRT" [unknown]
    - "Police State - Scene Three Dailies TRK HD", 1987; ID: 311.0051 (Film 311.0051)
    - "Police State" [Unmarked White Reel], 1987; ID: 311.0054 (Film 311.0054)
    - "Police State" [Unmarked Reel], 1987; ID: 311.0053 (Film 311.0053)
    - "Police State - Color Reversal B-Wind Head", c1987; ID: 311.0448 (Film 311.0448)
    - "Whoregasm Original", c1988; ID: 311.0042 (Film 311.0042)
    - "Whoregasm - Right Original", c1988; ID: 311.0056 (Film 311.0056)
    - "Nick Zedd - No Title", June 13, 1988; ID: 311.0043 (Film 311.0043)
    - "War is Menstrual Envy - Outtakes: Soldier Baby", 1992; ID: 311.0044 (Film 311.0044)
    - "War is Menstrual Envy - Workprint for Camera Rolls #3 and #1", 1992; ID: 311.0045 (Film 311.0045)
    - "War is Menstrual Envy - Outtakes: Kembra, Richard Chudnon, Annie Sprinkle", 1992; ID: 311.0046 (Film 311.0046)
    - "War is Menstrual Envy - Work Print Postive Roll A2", April 30, 1993; ID: 311.0047 (Film 311.0047)
    - "War is Menstrual Envy - Work Print Postive Octopus Cult, Dwarf, Ari Face, Roll A1", April 30, 1993; ID: 311.0048 (Film 311.0048)
    - "War is Menstrual Envy - Work Print Positive Roll A4", April 30, 1993; ID: 311.0049 (Film 311.0049)
    - "War is Menstrual Envy - Work Print Positive Roll A3", April 30, 1993; ID: 311.0050 (Film 311.0050)
    - "War is Menstrual Envy" [unmarked], October 18, 1990; ID: 311.0057 (Film 311.0057)
    - "War is Menstrual Envy" [unmarked], October 18, 1990; ID: 311.0058 (Film 311.0058)
    - "War is Menstrual Envy - Dwarf", October 18, 1990; ID: 311.0059 (Film 311.0059)
    - "War is Menstrual Envy - Octopus Cult Workprint Negative IMP", October 18, 1990; ID: 311.0060 (Film 311.0060)
    - "War is Menstrual Envy" [unmarked], October 18, 1990; ID: 311.0061 (Film 311.0061)
    - "War is Menstrual Envy - Tails Out Octopus Cult and Dwarf Negative", April 30, 1993; ID: 311.0062 (Film 311.0062)
    - "War is Menstrual Envy - A1 Contact Print Capt. Zero", January 11, 1993; ID: 311.0063 (Film 311.0063)
    - "War is Menstrual Envy - Workprint", April 22, 1993; ID: 311.0064 (Film 311.0064)
    - "War is Menstrual Envy - Credits, Kembra Fish, TV Footage, Credits Negative", July 2, 1992; ID: 311.0065 (Film 311.0065)
    - "War is Menstrual Envy - Credits, Kembra and Fish, Credits Negative", July 3, 1992; ID: 311.0066 (Film 311.0066)
    - "War is Menstrual Envy 3 - Workprint", c1992; ID: 311.0067 (Film 311.0067)
    - "War is Menstrual Envy 4 - World's Fair Negative", c1992; ID: 311.0068 (Film 311.0068)
    - "Lock Stock and Barrel" by Nick Zedd, Emma Diamond, and Mark Brady, 1994; ID: 311.0069 (Film 311.0069)
    - "Squeezebox '95 - R2 Negative", 1995; ID: 311.0070 (Film 311.0070)
      Squeezebox '95 - R2 Negative
    - "Squeezebox 1 & 2", 1995; ID: 311.0071 (Film 311.0071)
    - "Screen Tests - A Roll", January 1998; ID: 311.0072 (Film 311.0072)
    - "Screen Tests - Salonge, Daryl, Karen, Bob B Roll", January 1998; ID: 311.0073 (Film 311.0073)
    - "Why Do You Exist" [Unmarked Reel], 1998; ID: 311.0074 (Film 311.0074)
    - "Why Do You Exist" [Unmarked Reel], 1998; ID: 311.0075 (Film 311.0075)
    - "Why Do You Exist" [Unmarked Reel], 1998; ID: 311.0077 (Film 311.0077)
    - "Ecstasy in Entropy - Heads Original", c1999; ID: 311.0078 (Film 311.0078)
    - "Ecstasy in Entropy - Head Original", c1999; ID: 311.0079 (Film 311.0079)
    - "Ecstasy in Entropy - Outtakes", 2001; ID: 311.0083 (Film 311.0083)
    - "Imitation of Kiss [I of K9]", 2001; ID: 311.0001 (Film 311.0001)
    - "The Adventures of Electra Elf: Behind the Scenes Bluescreen Footage Negative", undated; ID: 311.0080 (Film 311.0080)
    - "Japan", undated; ID: 311.0081 (Film 311.0081)
    - "Mixed Misc. Footage", undated; ID: 311.0082 (Film 311.0082)
    - "Roll A Film Test Nick Zedd", undated; ID: 311.0090 (Film 311.0090)
    - "Rose PG-36", undated; ID: 311.0085 (Film 311.0085)
    - [Man Speaking to Crowd], undated; ID: 311.0086 (Film 311.0086)
    - [Person Sleeping in Bed], undated; ID: 311.0087 (Film 311.0087)